{
    "subject": "resource/Mephisto_(1981_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:East_German_films",
    "human_readable": "Mephisto (1981 film) is about East German films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6400850415229797,
            "question": "What is the significance of East German films in a broader cinematic context?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5865232348442078,
            "question": "What country are the films in Mephisto about from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.563033401966095,
            "question": "What year was the film Mephisto released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40742188692092896,
            "question": "What genre is the film Mephisto classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38056036829948425,
            "question": "Are there any other films that explore similar themes to Mephisto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37027740478515625,
            "question": "How did the film Mephisto perform critically and commercially?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27109742164611816,
            "question": "How might Mephisto be relevant to contemporary audiences today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2324400246143341,
            "question": "What historical context influenced the creation of Mephisto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18302536010742188,
            "question": "What themes does Mephisto likely explore based on its subject matter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10739436000585556,
            "question": "Who are some notable actors or directors associated with the film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mephisto (1981 film) is about East German films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6414_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes does Mephisto likely explore based on its subject matter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6414_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical context influenced the creation of Mephisto?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6414_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might Mephisto be relevant to contemporary audiences today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6414_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6414_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that *Mephisto* is a film set in Germany during the rise of Nazism, not East Germany.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention that Mephisto (1981 film) is about a German actor who rises to fame during the rise of Nazism in Germany, not East German films."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Mephisto (1981) is a film set during the rise of Nazism in Germany, not about East German films. Therefore, the statement that Mephisto (1981 film) is about East German films is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}